{"sid": "FWNJDZ5GM92B_main", "calc_equals_delay": 5, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 5, "start_time": 330073, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 330073, "question": "8+3+3+24", "correct_answer": 38, "events": [["submit", 338137]], "time_left_end": "292", "answered_time": 338137, "user_answer": "38", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "292", "question_time_start": 338138, "question": "17+34", "correct_answer": 51, "events": [["calc_1", 339954], ["calc_7", 340471], ["calc_+", 341121], ["calc_3", 341688], ["calc_4", 342071], ["calc_=", 342554], ["submit", 350660]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "280", "answered_time": 350660, "user_answer": "51", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "280", "question_time_start": 350660, "question": "7+3+6+7", "correct_answer": 23, "events": [["submit", 353644]], "time_left_end": "277", "answered_time": 353644, "user_answer": "23", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "277", "question_time_start": 353644, "question": "9+17", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 358006]], "time_left_end": "273", "answered_time": 358006, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "273", "question_time_start": 358006, "question": "7+7+17", "correct_answer": 31, "events": [["submit", 369175]], "time_left_end": "261", "answered_time": 369175, "user_answer": "31", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "261", "question_time_start": 369175, "question": "6+8+83", "correct_answer": 97, "events": [["submit", 392722]], "time_left_end": "238", "answered_time": 392722, "user_answer": "97", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "238", "question_time_start": 392723, "question": "3+4+3+6", "correct_answer": 16, "events": [["submit", 397472]], "time_left_end": "233", "answered_time": 397472, "user_answer": "16", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "233", "question_time_start": 397472, "question": "44+24", "correct_answer": 68, "events": [["submit", 402272]], "time_left_end": "228", "answered_time": 402272, "user_answer": "68", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "228", "question_time_start": 402273, "question": "8+6+83", "correct_answer": 97, "events": [["submit", 408089]], "time_left_end": "222", "answered_time": 408089, "user_answer": "97", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "222", "question_time_start": 408089, "question": "4+76", "correct_answer": 80, "events": [["submit", 412556]], "time_left_end": "218", "answered_time": 412556, "user_answer": "80", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 5, "start_time": 412556, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "218", "question_time_start": 412556, "question": "7+24", "correct_answer": 31, "events": [["submit", 416239]], "time_left_end": "214", "answered_time": 416239, "user_answer": "31", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "214", "question_time_start": 416239, "question": "87+73", "correct_answer": 160, "events": [["calc_8", 420123], ["calc_7", 420423], ["calc_+", 420890], ["calc_7", 421440], ["calc_3", 421906], ["calc_=", 422240], ["submit", 429806]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "201", "answered_time": 429806, "user_answer": "160", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "201", "question_time_start": 429806, "question": "3+8+29", "correct_answer": 40, "events": [["submit", 435057]], "time_left_end": "196", "answered_time": 435057, "user_answer": "40", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "196", "question_time_start": 435057, "question": "4+4+43", "correct_answer": 51, "events": [["submit", 441624]], "time_left_end": "189", "answered_time": 441624, "user_answer": "51", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "189", "question_time_start": 441624, "question": "3+3+4+47", "correct_answer": 57, "events": [["submit", 447107]], "time_left_end": "183", "answered_time": 447107, "user_answer": "57", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "183", "question_time_start": 447107, "question": "86+24", "correct_answer": 110, "events": [["submit", 451374]], "time_left_end": "179", "answered_time": 451374, "user_answer": "110", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "179", "question_time_start": 451374, "question": "7+6+4+3", "correct_answer": 20, "events": [["submit", 456157]], "time_left_end": "174", "answered_time": 456157, "user_answer": "20", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "174", "question_time_start": 456157, "question": "8+7+88", "correct_answer": 103, "events": [["submit", 467257]], "time_left_end": "163", "answered_time": 467257, "user_answer": "103", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "163", "question_time_start": 467258, "question": "6+3+6+6", "correct_answer": 21, "events": [["submit", 474675]], "time_left_end": "156", "answered_time": 474675, "user_answer": "21", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "156", "question_time_start": 474675, "question": "7+13", "correct_answer": 20, "events": [["submit", 477408]], "time_left_end": "153", "answered_time": 477408, "user_answer": "20", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 5, "start_time": 477408, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "153", "question_time_start": 477408, "question": "3+4+3+83", "correct_answer": 93, "events": [["submit", 489125]], "time_left_end": "141", "answered_time": 489125, "user_answer": "93", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "141", "question_time_start": 489125, "question": "6+7+94", "correct_answer": 107, "events": [["submit", 493375]], "time_left_end": "137", "answered_time": 493375, "user_answer": "107", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "137", "question_time_start": 493375, "question": "27+96", "correct_answer": 123, "events": [["submit", 503192]], "time_left_end": "127", "answered_time": 503192, "user_answer": "123", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "127", "question_time_start": 503192, "question": "6+3+96", "correct_answer": 105, "events": [["submit", 507742]], "time_left_end": "123", "answered_time": 507742, "user_answer": "105", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "123", "question_time_start": 507742, "question": "3+4+9+9", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 515242]], "time_left_end": "115", "answered_time": 515242, "user_answer": "25", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "115", "question_time_start": 515242, "question": "9+9+8+7", "correct_answer": 33, "events": [["submit", 529592]], "time_left_end": "101", "answered_time": 529592, "user_answer": "32", "user_correct": "False", "score": "24"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "101", "question_time_start": 529593, "question": "17+77", "correct_answer": 94, "events": [["submit", 537943]], "time_left_end": "93", "answered_time": 537943, "user_answer": "94", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "93", "question_time_start": 537943, "question": "8+63", "correct_answer": 71, "events": [["submit", 542376]], "time_left_end": "88", "answered_time": 542376, "user_answer": "71", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "88", "question_time_start": 542376, "question": "9+4+14", "correct_answer": 27, "events": [["submit", 550660]], "time_left_end": "80", "answered_time": 550660, "user_answer": "27", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "80", "question_time_start": 550660, "question": "3+84", "correct_answer": 87, "events": [["submit", 555160]], "time_left_end": "75", "answered_time": 555160, "user_answer": "87", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 5, "start_time": 555160, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "75", "question_time_start": 555160, "question": "8+23", "correct_answer": 31, "events": [["submit", 559077]], "time_left_end": "71", "answered_time": 559077, "user_answer": "31", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "71", "question_time_start": 559077, "question": "64+78", "correct_answer": 142, "events": [["calc_6", 562777], ["calc_4", 563194], ["calc_+", 563743], ["calc_7", 564393], ["calc_8", 564677], ["calc_=", 565243], ["submit", 572527]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "58", "answered_time": 572527, "user_answer": "142", "user_correct": "True", "score": "30"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "58", "question_time_start": 572527, "question": "3+3+46", "correct_answer": 52, "events": [["submit", 577143]], "time_left_end": "53", "answered_time": 577143, "user_answer": "52", "user_correct": "True", "score": "31"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "53", "question_time_start": 577144, "question": "4+7+33", "correct_answer": 44, "events": [["submit", 583210]], "time_left_end": "47", "answered_time": 583210, "user_answer": "44", "user_correct": "True", "score": "32"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "47", "question_time_start": 583211, "question": "9+3+8+6", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 591244]], "time_left_end": "39", "answered_time": 591244, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "33"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "39", "question_time_start": 591244, "question": "38+33", "correct_answer": 71, "events": [["submit", 595061]], "time_left_end": "36", "answered_time": 595061, "user_answer": "71", "user_correct": "True", "score": "34"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "36", "question_time_start": 595061, "question": "9+7+9+6", "correct_answer": 31, "events": [["submit", 606327]], "time_left_end": "24", "answered_time": 606327, "user_answer": "31", "user_correct": "True", "score": "35"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "24", "question_time_start": 606327, "question": "3+3+87", "correct_answer": 93, "events": [["submit", 610678]], "time_left_end": "20", "answered_time": 610678, "user_answer": "93", "user_correct": "True", "score": "36"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "20", "question_time_start": 610678, "question": "3+3+8+28", "correct_answer": 42, "events": [["submit", 620395]], "time_left_end": "10", "answered_time": 620395, "user_answer": "42", "user_correct": "True", "score": "37"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "10", "question_time_start": 620395, "question": "3+33", "correct_answer": 36, "events": [["submit", 623028]], "time_left_end": "8", "answered_time": 623028, "user_answer": "36", "user_correct": "True", "score": "38"}}}, "block_4": {"mean_level": 5, "start_time": 623029, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "8", "question_time_start": 623029, "question": "13+98", "correct_answer": 111, "events": [["submit", 628562]], "time_left_end": "2", "answered_time": 628562, "user_answer": "112", "user_correct": "False", "score": "37"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "2", "question_time_start": 628562, "question": "4+8+79", "correct_answer": 91, "events": []}}}}}